export const data = {
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How would you describe your social interactions and connections?",
      "options": [
        "Fulfilling and frequent+0",
        "Occasionally satisfying+1",
        "Infrequent but satisfying+2",
        "Consistently lonely+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Consistently lonely"
    },
    {
      "question": "How often do you engage in social activities or spend time with friends and family?",
      "options": [
        "Regularly+0",
        "Occasionally+1",
        "Rarely+2",
        "Almost never+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Almost never"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you feel a sense of isolation or disconnection from others?",
      "options": [
        "Never+0",
        "Rarely+1",
        "Sometimes+2",
        "Frequently+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Frequently"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you noticed changes in your social habits or a decrease in social interactions?",
      "options": [
        "No changes+0",
        "Slight changes+1",
        "Moderate changes+2",
        "Significant changes+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Significant changes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you sought professional help or been diagnosed with loneliness or related issues?",
      "options": [
        "Yes+3",
        "Considering it+2",
        "No, not yet+1",
        "No, and I don't plan to+0"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Considering it"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do feelings of loneliness impact your daily life and well-being?",
      "options": [
        "Low impact+0",
        "Moderate impact+1",
        "High impact+2",
        "Very high impact+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "High impact"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you often experience a lack of emotional support or understanding from others?",
      "options": [
        "Never+0",
        "Rarely+1",
        "Sometimes+2",
        "Frequently+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Frequently"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have others expressed concern about your social isolation or loneliness?",
      "options": [
        "Never+0",
        "Rarely+1",
        "Sometimes+2",
        "Frequently+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Frequently"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you believe that addressing and managing loneliness is important for overall well-being?",
      "options": [
        "Strongly agree+3",
        "Agree+2",
        "Neutral+1",
        "Disagree+0"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Strongly agree"
    },
    {
      "question": "How long have you been experiencing feelings of loneliness?",
      "options": [
        "A short period+0",
        "Several months+1",
        "Years+2",
        "I haven't experienced feelings of loneliness+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Years"
    }
  ]
}
